http://promoxy.mirrors.phpclasses.org/faq/#privacy-policy

Help
Recommend this page to a friend!
Contents
What is the "PHP Classes Repository"?
What PHP classes are available?
How can I contribute with my own PHP classes?
How can I know when new classes are made available?
Why do I need to register to download the class files?
How much does it cost to register in this site?
What is the site refund policy?
What is the site privacy policy?
Will I get spam messages if I register in this site?
How do I unsubscribe from the site mailing lists?
Why do I still get messages after I have unsubscribed?
How can I delete my account?
How can I advertise on this site?
How do I contact the site administration to obtain further assistance?
What is the "PHP Classes Repository"?
PHP Classes Repository is a service created in 1999 as a means of distributing freely available programming classes of objects written in the Web scripting language named PHP. The goal of this service is to build a base of programming components ready to be used in applications written in PHP.
Contents
What PHP classes are available?
Initially, only classes developed by the site creator, Manuel Lemos, were available.
But some time after the creation of this repository, other developers started to contribute with their own classes. You may browse the available classes by entering the browse page.
Contents
How can I contribute with my own PHP classes?
To contribute, first you need to register. Once you have logged in, you create packages for your classes. Then you may either import your package files from a version control repository site (Git or Subversion or CVS) or upload upload the files of the packages manually.
Contents
How can I know when new classes are made available?
The site registered users may be notified by e-mail when a new class is added or updated.
Contents
Why do I need to register to download the class files?
This site allows any user to download any class packages files without being registered, as long as the authors of the packages express that they do not wish that the site makes a more accurate accounting of users that download their packages.
So authors have the possibility to configure an option to determine whether the users are required to register and login in order to download the files of their packages.
If users are not logged when they download a package, it is not possible for the site to accurately keep track of the users that downloaded the package.
Therefore, many authors prefer to keep the login requirement, so the downloads of their packages can be accounted for and the packages can feature in the top download charts.
Also, when a package is updated, the site can notify by e-mail users who were logged in when they downloaded that package. Users that are not interested in being notified by e-mail may set their personal options to not receive such notifications.
Many authors appreciate this automated notification service as it helps keep their package users up to date. Sending e-mail notifications when a package is updated also helps authors saving time providing support to users who might not have upgraded to newer versions with bug fixes and improved features.
Contents
How much does it cost to register in this site?
The registration in this site is absolutely free of charge. The site provides an additional set of services to users that buy a premium subscription or post jobs. But nobody is required to pay anything to become a regular registered user.
Contents
What is the site refund policy?
Users that purchase premium subscriptions may request a refund when they wish to cancel a subscription upto 7 days after it was automatically renewed and they did not cancel before the subscription period ended.
Users that purchased job posting credits may also request a refund upto 7 days after the credits were purchased if none of the purchased credits was used.
Refund requests should be sent to the site contact address.
Contents
What is the site privacy policy?
The personal information supplied by registered users will not be shared with any entity unrelated with the site.
Such personal information includes the personal name, user account name that can be used to log in the site, e-mail address, birth date, country of origin and personal picture. Exceptions may happen in the following specific cases:
a) authors who submit content to the site and have their personal names and picture exposed on the same pages on which their content is published
b) users who claim prizes in contests organized by the site, in which the users voluntarily participate and authorize the site to supply their e-mail address to the sponsors who will contact them to deliver the prizes.
Third party vendors, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this site or other sites.
Advertising networks' use cookies to enable them to serve ads to this site users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting the site www.aboutads.info .
Contents
Will I get spam messages if I register in this site?
No. As stated in the policy privacy, this site will not share your e-mail address with any entity unrelated with the site.
The registered users' e-mail address is required mainly to prevent users creating multiple accounts that could be used to distort the download accounting statistics or to commit fraud in the several types of voting systems on the site.
The site also uses the registered users' e-mail address to send messages of their interest through several types of site mailing lists, like for instance alert messages when new content is available or newsletters with important announcements related to site features.
Contents
How do I unsubscribe from the site mailing lists?
Users who do not wish to receive the site newsletters and alert messages, can unsubscribe from them by following the instructions at the bottom of such messages.
One way to unsubscribe from a mailing list is to send a blank message to an address mentioned at the bottom of the mailing list messages you receive. In response, the site will send you another message with the URL of a special page that you need to access to confirm the unsubscribe request.
When unsubscribing by e-mail, make sure you are sending a message from the same e-mail address used to subscribe. Otherwise, the site may not find your account and your unsubscription request is ignored.
Note that there are several types of mailing lists. Users can only send one unsubscribe request by e-mail at a time.
You should get a message with further instructions in response to your unsubscription request. If you do not get the message in 24 hours after you send your request, please contact the site administration for further assistance.
An alternative way to unsubscribe is to log in the user options page and uncheck the options respective to the mailing lists you are not interested. This way multiple list can be unsubscribed in one go.
Contents
Why do I still get messages after I have unsubscribed?
This may happen under several circumstances:
1. You have sent an unsubscribe request message by e-mail but you have not confirmed the request. When the site receives an unsubscribe request message, it sends a message to the user with an URL of a page that the user has to access to confirm the request and complete the unsubscribe process.
If you have not gone to the page mentioned in the confirmation request message, you need to go there or else you remain subscribed. If you did not receive that message yet, please wait at least 24 hours and try again.
2. You may have unsubscribed from a mailing list that has queued a message for you but it is not possible to cancel that delivery. If you have unsubscribed recently, please allow at least 24 hours to let the mailing list system finish current deliveries that may be in progress.
3. The site has several types of mailing lists. You may have unsubscribed only from one mailing list but you have not unsubscribed from others. In this case, follow the instructions to unsubscribe.
4. You may have another account under a different e-mail address. Take a look at the To: header of the messages that you receive to determine the e-mail address of that account. When you send the unsubscribe request message, make sure that the From: header of that message indicates that account e-mail address.
Contents
How can I delete my account?
The site supports the permanent removal of any accounts as there is no interest to retain personal information of users that no longer want to use the site.
When a user wants that he or she no longer wants to access the site, the user can access a the user options page to request the removal of his or her account by clicking on the Account tab and then on the Request account removal.
When that happens, the site will wipe personal information details in a way that the original personal information cannot be recovered from the site database.
Personal information details include the user name used to log in the site, personal name, email address, birth date, country of origin or personal pictures.
The user name and the email address information is replaced by random text that is a one way hash value.
This hash value can be used to detect if another user tries to register in the site with the same user name or email address of another user that registered in the past but requested that the site removes his or her account.
Contents
How can I advertise on this site?
There are several opportunities to advertise on this site as a sponsor. Please visit the sponsorship page and submit the sponsor inquiry form with details about your advertising purposes.
Contents
How do I contact the site administration to obtain further assistance?
The site administration is often very busy. It may take several days before you receive human assistance. Therefore, please read the answers to the questions above to verify whether what you want to achieve is already explained here.
If you are not able to achieve what you want using the information in this page, you may contact the site administration by sending a message to info at phpclasses dot org.
Contents
Advertise on this site
Site map
Newsletter
Statistics
Site tips
Privacy policy
Contact
For more information send a message to info at phpclasses dot org.
